Unicode Fonts for Ancient Scripts
http://users.teilar.gr/~g1951d/

George Douros
g1951d@teilar.gr

2010

In lieu of a licence:
Fonts in ‘Unicode Fonts for Ancient Scripts’ are offered free for any use; they may be opened, edited, modified, regenerated, posted, packaged and redistributed.

_____________________________
Maya.otf
Version 1.06
Maya is not a merchandise.

Maya covers the glyphs in J. Eric S. Thompson’s “A Catalog of Maya Hieroglyphs”, as well as some extra glyphs for days, months and numbers. This is a work-font that may be of some scholarly use; it is not a proposal of any kind. There are no plans to improve or expand it. Maya.pdf provides further information.