Unicode Fonts for Ancient Scripts
http://users.teilar.gr/~g1951d/

George Douros
g1951d@teilar.gr

2010

In lieu of a licence:
Fonts in ‘Unicode Fonts for Ancient Scripts’ are offered free for any use; they may be opened, edited, modified, regenerated, posted, packaged and redistributed.

_____________________________
Anatolian.otf
Version 3.06
Anatolian is not a merchandise.

Anatolian is a work-font, encoding Anatolian Hieroglyphs in F200 - F4FF of the Private Use Area of the BMP. There are no plans to improve or expand it. Anatolian.pdf provides further information.